NOAH LANGE

(920) 455-0511 2367 Jourdain Ln. Green Bay, WI, 54301 noahrlange.gmail.com

Intelligent and articulate college student with experience in writing, publishing, computer science, journalism, radio, web design and web development. Highly adaptive, quick to grasp new ideas and tasks as well as unfamiliar software and computer systems. Able to communicate readily and clearly in speech and word.

Programming, web design and web management – including experience with Python, Java, C++, C# and web technologies.

Graphic design - including proficiency with the Adobe Creative Suite software.

Radio disc jockeying and audio production with Adobe Audition, Apple GarageBand and Audacity.

Skilled writer of fiction and non-fiction.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Website Manager & Design Technician, Luther College Chips

September 2011 - May 2014

- Managed the award-winning website and upgraded the Drupal distribution for the weekly college newspaper, Chips.
- Modernized dated design of newspaper and worked as the in-house design technician, editing photographs, creating info-graphics and performing miscellaneous graphic design duties.

Summer Station Manager & Sunday Board Operator, KWLC Decorah

September 2011 - May 2014

- Worked at KWLC Decorah as one of three summer staff members, covering twenty-plus hours a week onair as a DJ, as well as performing another twenty hours of managerial duties and curating the station's archives.
- Worked for several years as one of two Sunday Board Operators, responsible for broadcasting live and pre-recorded material.

Interpreter, Mackinac State Historic Parks

September 2013 - August 2013

• Worked as a historical interpreter at Colonial Michilimackinac and the Old Mackinac Point Lighthouse. Gave tours, demonstrations and engaged with visitors.

Editor, KWLC The AM

September 2011 - May 2012

• Re-established an original publication of Luther College's radio station, KWLC Decorah. Duties included writing, curating and editing submissions and establishing a new visual identity through extensive graphic design work, as well as training a succeeding editor for the subsequent academic year.

Cashier at Golden & Jaguar Shell

May 2011 - August 2011

• Managed inventories and invoices for incoming shipments, performed bookkeeping tasks, worked at cash register and customer service, organizing and maintaining product stock.

EDUCATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Luther College Class of 2014, B.A. in English and Computer Science

September 2010 - May 2014

- Luther College Dean's List 2010 2014
- Participant in Honors Program